(Sheldon:)with my driver Ganesh.
(Penny:)Fine.
Oh, thanks!
You're a peach!
(Sheldon:)Beverly, we'll
catch up soon.
(Sheldon:)Bernadette, it was
a pleasure as always,
(Sheldon:)Penny, you have
spinach in your teeth.
(door closes)
(Penny:)How long have I had spinach
in my teeth?
(Beverly:)Since the airport, dear.
(Howard:)You look like you come
with a kickstand.
(Raj:)You can't make me feel bad.
(Howard:)Hmm, maybe not. Leonard?
(Leonard:)So, when the aliens
brought you back,
(Leonard:)they just left the probe in?
(Sheldon:)I'm back.
(Leonard:)Hey, how'd it go?
It went well.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I've learned that
if you never say you're sorry,
(Sheldon:)the times you do really
puts them on their heels.
(Sheldon:)Uh, Stuart, I relieve you
of your line duties.
(Stuart:)Anyone else need
anything before I go?
(Howard:)I'll give you a dollar
if make fun of Raj.
(Stuart:)That's mean.
Five.
(Stuart:)You look like Tigger
if Tigger looked like a jackass.